残酷な天使のように 少年よ 神話になれ
青い風が今 胸のドアを叩いても 私だけをただ見つめて 微笑んでるあなた
そっと触れるもの 求めることに夢中で 運命さえまだ知らない 痛い気な瞳
だけどいつか気づくでしょう その背中には
遥か未来 目指すための羽があること
残酷な天使の体勢 窓辺からやがて取り立つ
もっと走る熱いパトスで 思い出を裏切るなら
この空を抱いて輝く 少年よ 神話になれ
ileption 狂山が明らかしてよ
未来 それらの顔もらえ張り特別に通過
信話が明るかもうelpu代 エネルゼロー salvation
クッキーーペーで燃 hat
エペのるいし爆料
目指すエネルゼロスで 指指さを押す
リポイントに計帶 たい
the target has gone silent what's Shinji status he's alive
I'm going to the cage take over for me please the pilot's brain waves are extremely erratic
this cardiac readings are very weak increase the power to the life support systems give him
a heart massage Roger heartbeat stabilized forcey check the entry plug hurry emergency
LCL discharge Roger come on open the hatch come on
Shinji
the
it's accelerated particle beam cannon has hit the balloon the decoys been vaporized next
one
the
mortar has been vaporized
yeah I see that
from the data we've collected we're assuming the angel automatically attacks any opponents to come within a certain range
so there's a 100% probability that anything that enters that range will be targeted it's too risky for close-range combat in an Ava isn't it
what's the status of its AT field it's still active it's strong enough that the spatial changes in pays are visible
and needless to say using conventional means of attack guided missiles artillery and bombs would inflict more damage on us than on the angel
yeah offensively and defensively it's almost perfect a real flying fortress what's the angels current location
at this moment the target is directly above us penetrating the Tokyo 3 null zone a giant shield with a diameter of 17.5 meters is boring towards nerve HQ
that's it then it appears the enemy is going to attack nerve headquarters directly
sassy bastard
what's its estimated time of arrival
six minutes 54 seconds a.m. just after midnight
by that time it will have breached all 22 levels of defense armor and will penetrate headquarters itself
less than 10 hours
the shield has contacted the first armor plate
ah what kind of condition is unit 1 in
well unit 1's defensive armor was melted down to the third layer
but the good news is that the central control unit sustained no damage
given three more seconds it would have shot right through the Ava
it will take three hours to install replacement parts
understood what's unit 0 status
the reactivation of unit 0 shouldn't prove a problem
but there's still a feedback error remaining
so it wouldn't survive combat
what's the condition of unit 1's pilot
no physical damage however nerve pulses are up by 0.8
that's still within the acceptable limits
enemy arrival 9 hours 55 minutes
talk about high pressure situations
why don't we raise a white flag
before we do that there's just one more little thing that i'd like to try
you want to use a sniper to shoot the target from outside its firing zone
yes sir instead of trying to neutralize the target's AT field
i believe a pinpoint shot with a focused high energy beam is the only way
what did the magi say
the responses from the magi supercomputers were two affirmative and one conditional affirmative
our probability of success is eight point seven percent
it's the highest value we could get
i see no reason to reject your plan
you may proceed captain katsuraki
yes sir
you know how crazy this whole operation is don't you
operations director katsuraki
don't be rude it's not crazy
it can be done within nine hours and has the highest chance of success
it does really but our positron rifle can't handle such a high output
what are you going to do about that
if ours won't work we'll borrow one
we'll borrow one
you don't mean
yeah the ssdf's new prototype
i've come on behalf of nerve to hereby requisition the prototype self-propelled positron cannon as of 1500 hours today
but this is just so ridiculous
we'll do our best to return this in as close to its original condition as we can
thank you for your cooperation have a nice day
it's all yours ray take it away
what the
be careful that's a piece of precision machinery
but ma'am our latest calculations show that it'll take at least 180 million kilowatts to penetrate that angel's at field
just where exactly are you planning on getting that much electricity
where do you think i'll get it all over japan
we apologize for interrupting our regular programming for this emergency bulletin
from 11 30 pm tonight until tomorrow morning
there will be a large scale power blackout throughout most of japan
we appreciate your cooperation
repeat from 11 30 pm tonight until tomorrow morning
there will be a large scale power blackout throughout most of japan
we appreciate your cooperation
the shield has just broken through the seventh defensive layer
what's the status on the energy supply system
uh... we're running about 3.2 percent behind schedule
but we should be finished by 2310
and the positron rifle?
for the honor of technology development department section 3
we bet that we'll have it built in 3 hours
and how's our defense coming?
well a shield is about the best we can come up with
so is this the shield?
yes it was sort of part of the space shuttle
it may look ugly but it's got an electromagnetic base coating
that section 2 guarantees will stand up to the enemy's particle beam
for at least 17 seconds
pretty impressive huh?
good work Ritsuko
what about the sniper position?
taking geographical features and access to power transformers into consideration
this is our best choice
right everything's looking good
our sniper will attack from the top of Mount Futago
we will commence at zero hours tomorrow morning
from this point on this operation is called Operation Yashima
roger
now the only remaining problem is the pilot
unit 1's pilot is conscious now
his examination results look normal
good then the operation will proceed as planned
roger
but i wonder if he'll pilot it again
let's get to Mount Futago now
now
ianami
pilot akari
i've been sent here to brief you on the operation yashima timetables
the operation will begin at midnight zero hundred hours
prior to that pilots ikari and ayunami will arrive at the cage by 1730
at 1800 unit 1 and unit 0 will activate
at 1805 both units will be deployed
they will arrive at the temporary base at Mount Futago at 1830
there they will await for their orders
here
this is a new one
don't show up looking like that pilot akari
oh
sorry
i've been apologizing since yesterday
your meal
i don't feel like eating anything
we will be departing in 60 minutes
do i really have to pilot ava again
yes
you do
i don't want to
you can be so cool about it because you haven't had the kind of experiences i've had yet
i don't want to go through it again
then you can just stay here in bed
uh
what do you mean by that
i will pilot ava unit 1
dr okagi is already prepared to rewrite the personal data files for unit 1
ritsuko is
captain katsuragi and dr okagi will be waiting for me in the cage
hey
goodbye
bye
they're really late
we ought to evacuate to the shelter
no way
i hacked into my dad's data files
i'm absolutely sure this is the time it's said
This is the time it's said.
Well, okay then.
Where in the heck are they?
The entire mountain is moving.
There they are, it's the Evangelions!
Totally awesome!
Go for it, Evangelions!
We've been leaving you!
We've been leaving you, yeah!
Go without you!
Yeah!
The shield has penetrated through the 17th layer of armor.
It will reach headquarters in three hours, 55 minutes.
Power supply stations from Shikoko and Kyosho areas completed.
Beginning tests of each cooling system.
That's a very delicate piece of machinery.
Handle it carefully.
This thing wasn't built for field operations.
Will it really work?
Point taken.
But we have no choice.
This was the most expedient way of achieving our goal.
Aren't you sure it's safe to use?
Theoretically, yes.
However, we're not sure if the cannon barrel and accelerator will be able to handle the stress or not.
This is the first time it's ever been fired with such a high power output behind it.
Listen up!
Here are the battle plans for the operation.
Shinji!
Yes?
Your Unit 1 will be the gunner.
Right.
Ray, you will cover him with Unit 0.
Yes.
The reason for this arrangement is because Shinji has a higher sync ratio with Unit 1,
and this operation will require an exceptionally high degree of precision.
Since the positron beam will be influenced by the Earth's gravity, magnetic fields, and rotation,
it will not fire in a straight line.
You must remember to adjust for these deviations.
You must penetrate the core precisely.
But, Ritsuko, I've never practiced with this before.
Don't worry.
Just do what the manual says.
As soon as the indicators in the center converge, just pull the trigger.
The computers will handle the rest.
Also, be aware that before you can fire the rifle a second time,
you will first have to wait for the Unit to cool.
Then replace the fuses and reload.
You've got to hit it the first time.
What if I miss?
Or the enemy shoots back?
Shinji, don't even think about something like that.
You've got to destroy the Angel with your first shot.
So I have no choice.
I... I'm just to defend Unit One, is that correct?
Yes.
Understood.
It's time. Get geared up.
Right.
Maybe...
This will be our last day alive.
Why would you say something like that?
You won't die.
Huh?
I'll be protecting you.
Keep going.
So much to pass away.
What?
We hope to get yourmana, one of you will find you ever at Heaven?
What you wanted to start with?
Yes.
Well, you could get a good picture.
Well, before you look out.
Now, I'm just going to get my Shortly Saloon.
I was I.
Big mirrors.
We do not.
I'm I.
I was.
Over in the back.
Ayanami, just why do you pilot this thing?
Because I'm bonded to it.
You're bonded?
Yes. It's a bond.
You mean to my father?
To all people.
You're very strong, Rei.
I have nothing else.
What do you mean you have nothing else?
It's time. Let's go.
Goodbye, Shinji.
The time is approaching zero hundred hours.
Commencing operation.
Listen, Shinji.
We're entrusting you with the energy of the entire nation of Japan.
I'm counting on you.
Roger.
Initiate primary connection. Do it!
Initiating power transmission from districts numbers one through eight oh three.
Voltage is rising. Water exchange unit reaching pressure zone.
All cooling systems operating on full power.
Temperature stable. No problems detected.
Roger. Positron charge is nominal.
Initiate second connection.
All accelerators are engaging.
Activate the convergence unit now.
Transmitting all power to Mount Futago, temporary substation.
No problems reported with third connection.
Release final safety systems.
Release final safety lock.
Error correction for Earth rotation and gravity is 0.0009.
Voltage is 0.2 short of critical.
Zero.
Seven and tenth connections engaged.
Transmitting all energy to the positron rifle.
Nine, eight, seven, six, five, three, two, one.
High energy output detected inside target.
No, not again.
Three, two, one.
Fire now.
No!
Did we miss?
The enemy shield has broken into the geo-front!
Hurry! Second shot!
Replacing fuses! Initiating recharge!
Feral cooling in progress!
We've got another high-energy reading building inside the target!
Not now!
Look out, Shinji!
Iyanami!
The shield can't last long!
Hurry, Freddy!
Ten more seconds!
Hurry up!
Yeah, we made it!
Iyanami!
Are you alright?
Don't ever say that!
Just don't say that you have nothing else!
Just don't say that!
And don't say goodbye when you look at me!
Iyanami!
Are you all right?!
Don't ever say that!
Just don't say that you have nothing else!
Just don't say that!
And don't say goodbye when you leave on a mission.
on a mission, it's just too sad.
Why are you crying?
I'm very sorry.
I don't know what I should do or feel at a time like this.
Why don't you just try smiling?
Oh, let me play among the stars.
Let me see what spring is like.
Won't you be down on Mars?
In other words, hold my hand.
In other words, do me, kiss me.
Feel my heart without, and let me see forever more.
You are all I love for, I want to panadour.
In other words, do me, kiss me, kiss me.
In other words, I won't be.
When a giant humanoid-type robot created by a civilian corporation
goes out of control during its official test trial,
it's up to EVA Unit 1 to catch the rampaging jet alone.
Will Misato be able to stop its nuclear reactor from melting down?
Find out in the next exciting episode.
As if you Braunom casigasm.
Continués.
You got one question.
What?
flix-in-hemp.
Please ask me to get him.
Spongebob.
What?
People dabei before they check out theurs
I want to advance.
Once you have open, I feel them.
Looking at theurban games they come to look how
Thank you for the CBT.
Okay, thank you for the most important.
departure, uh, sorry.
doo.
A battle is Janeyane, Mar苦 дерев,
This timey walk to Kyuu.
Kiko Kiko'i is a good star.
Each player of克服 is a freshisce option to pick up